本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.com
翻译：  Echo 莫若謙 好战青蛙 五枚の夜堇 将错就错
校对：  爽爷  谭亚平     后期： 小滔
觅迹寻踪
# 值此一夜 义无反顾 #
# 大街小巷迎接每一个行路之人 #
# 这是迷失灵魂的必经之路 #
# 笑容不曾正视双眸 #
# 戴上面具 伪装自己 #
# 周围一切 如此欣欣向荣 #
# 即便只有孤独陪伴左右 #
# 昨日浮现 莫名的街巷 飘落的花朵 #
# 逝去的时光如此甜美 #
# 如今只有心有所思 孤独前行 #
# 一举一动 看似随意 #
# 原来都因同一目的 #
# 却不知一切只是徒劳 #
# 这是迷失灵魂的必经之路 #
# 笑容不曾正视双眸 #
# 戴上面具 伪装自己 #
# 周围一切 如此欣欣向荣 #
# 即便只有孤独陪伴左右 #
# 在光亮和阴影之下 #
# 不幸的秘密挥之不去 #
# 为何它出现在此? #
# 为何怨念如此深重 不曾褪去 #
# 在深夜 请告诉我 #
# 没有任何事物可以逃脱你的慧眼 #
# 这是迷失灵魂的必经之路 #
# 笑容不曾正视双眸 #
# 戴上面具 伪装自己 #
# 周围一切 如此欣欣向荣 #
# 即便只有孤独陪伴左右 #
# 笑容不曾正视双眸 #
# 戴上面具 伪装自己 #
# 周围一切 如此欣欣向荣 #
# 即便只有孤独陪伴左右 #
早上好 长官
Good morning sir.
我是达夫拉
这里发生什么事情?
What happened in here?
一起交通事故 长官 有辆车冲到海里去了
It's an accident sir. The car went into the ocean.
长官 我对您久仰大名
I have heard so much about you sir.
有机会与您共事 一定十分愉快
It will be fun to work with you sir.
那辆车突然加速 然后右转 坠到海里去了
The car suddently came speeding, made a turn and fell into the sea.
事发时 你在哪里?
Where were you?
我当时就坐在那里
I was sitting there.
长官
sir.
长官 当时粉妞知道要发生事情
Sir Pinky knew something was going to happen.
她提示我
She told me.
但是我并没有留意
but I did not listen to her.
粉妞是谁?
Who is Pinky?
长官 您好!
Greetings sir!
当时马路上面只有那一辆车
It was only one car on the road that time.
当时马路上面有任何障碍物吗?
Was there any thing in the middle of the road?
马路上面什么也没有 长官
There was nothing there sir.
我亲眼目睹了一切
I saw everything with my own eyes.
长官 请过来一下
Sir please come here.
阿尔曼·卡普尔
That is Arman Kapoor.
仔细检查他的身份信息
Check his identification details.
车是从内部反锁的 长官
The car was locked from inside sir.
死者身上的安全带没有解开
The body still had his seat belt on.
的确是他本人 长官
He is the one, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是怎么回事?
What is happening here?
大家请离开 可以请大家离开这里吗?
Please everyone move away from here.Can you please ask them to go away from here?
我们一定会查明真相的
We will be able to find out what happened.
请您签字
Sign this please.
我们的司机呢? 拉姆...
Our driver? Ramu...
卡普尔先生本人亲自开车的
Mr Kapoor was driving the car by himself.
他是一个人
He is alone.
一个人吗?
Alone?
他的助理尤弗雷
Yuvray his spot boy.
他在哪里?
Where was he?
他和阿尔曼形影不离
He is always with Arman.
车内没有其他人
There was nobody else in the car.
阿尔曼...
Arman...
阿尔曼绝对不会独处
Arman never stayed alone.
我真的不明白
I don't get it.
他为什么亲自开车? 他讨厌开车.
Why was he driving?He hates driving.
联系拉姆和尤弗雷这两个人
Get Ramu and Yuvray contact number
并且和他们谈谈
and talk to them.
妈妈 早上好
Good morning mom.
妈妈 发生什么事情?
Mom what happened?
著名影星阿尔曼·卡普尔于昨天晚上
Film star Arman Kapoor past away
在西普利斯路遭遇车祸 不幸丧生
in a tragic car accident at Sipleas Road last night.
西普利斯路位于孟买著名的
Sipleas Road is Mumbai's famous.
红灯区
red area.
那么阿尔曼·卡普尔
But what was Armaan Kapoor.
来这里做什么呢?
doing here?
哥们
Brother.
阿尔曼·卡普尔死了
Armaan Kapoor died.
什么?
What?
就是那个演员阿尔曼·卡普尔
Armaan Kapoor that actor,
他昨天晚上在西普利斯路发生车祸死了
died here at Sipleas road.
你说什么?
What are you talking?
我从那边过来的
I am coming from there.
大家都在谈论这起车祸
Everyone is talking about it.
新闻媒体在采访相关人员
Media were interviewing everyone.
这么说 昨天晚上 你真的和他见面了吗?
So, it's true that you met him last night?
我还以为你在开玩笑
I thought you were kidding.
谁和他见面了?
Who met him?
喂 闭嘴!
Hey shut up!
你还能单腿走路 不是吗?
You only can walk with one leg, right?
你就知足吧
Better appreciate it.
他嘴里就没有一句好话
Every time he brings a bad news.
拿着这个 给我买点早饭
Take this and bring my breakfast.
快去!
Go!
你骂那个可怜的男人做什么呢?
Why you like to scold that poor man?
无论我私下和你说的什么话
Whatever I discuss with you in private,
你不要和外人谈及此事
you should not mention it in front of everyone.
明白吗?
Do you understand?
抱歉
Sorry.
我不是向你道歉了吗?
Didn't I said sorry to you?
我此刻就站在阿尔曼·卡普尔的住所门前
I'm standing here right in front of Armaan Kapoor's resident.
从早上起 就有人陆续登门拜访...
Since morning a lot of people are visiting...
索尼娅在哪里?
Where is Sonia?
楼上
Upstairs.
达夫拉 过来
Come, Davraj.
坐
Seat down.
向我汇报一下情况
Now tell me.
阿尔曼·卡普尔先生三月四日晚上在电影城
Sir Armaan Kapoor was at Film City on 4th March night shooting
为制片人迪帕克·劳瓦尼拍摄电影
for producer Deepak Lalwani's movie.
凌晨两点结束拍摄工作
Shooting finish around 2 in the morning.
收工! 阿尔曼 枪法不错
Pack up! Good shoot Armaan.
收工之后 他的司机和助理都不在他的身边
At that time his driver and his assistent were not with him.
你和他们谈过吗?
You manage to talk to them?
是的 我已经和他们谈过了 长官
Yes, I did talk to them sir.
他们说 收工之后
They told me after pack up
他用十五分钟的时间更换衣服
he took 15 minuates to change his cloths.
然后他的助理像往常一样
And after that his assisstant kept all his stuff
把他的所有的行李放回车里去
in his car as usual.
但是那一天
But on that day,
他让他们直接从摄影棚回家
he asked them to go home from the studio itself
他表示要自己开车离开
and he drove his car himself.
拉姆
Ramu.
你回去吧 今天我自己开车
you go home. I will drive myself today.
快点... 快点
Faster... faster.
拉姆觉得有点奇怪
Even Ramu felt it weired
因为阿尔曼不喜欢自己开车
becouse Armaan don't like driving car himself.
他几点从电影城离开的?
What time did he go out from Film City?
凌晨两点二十分
At 2.20am.
可是他在凌晨四点发生的车祸
And his accident happened at 4 o'clock in the morning.
从电影城到西普利斯路有多远的距离?
What is the distance from Film City to Sipleas Road?
晚上开车的话 大概需要半个小时的时间
At night, it will take about half an hour.
假设他用了四十五分钟的时间
Even if he took 45 minuets.
那么在剩余的一个小时的时间里面 他在哪里?
Where was he in the extra 1 hour?
我对此毫不知情 长官
I have no information about that sir.
发生车祸的西普利斯路
Sipleas Road where his accident happen
和他家的方向 并不一致
is not going to his house direction.
西卡瓦特督查
Inspector Shikawat.
长官 您好 我们是印度时代周刊的记者
Sir, I'm calling from Time's of India.
我们致电确认一件事情
Would like to confirm a story.
我们得知 阿尔曼·卡普尔的手机上面
We came to know that there was an identified phone number
有一条已被确认的手机号码
found in Armaan Kapoor's mobile.
这条消息是否属实?
Is it true that...?
他的手机在海水里浸泡之后有所损坏
His mobile is not working as it drawn in the water
手机还在修理之中
and still under repairing.
谁和媒体记者谈过?
Who talks to the press?
告诉我 你们当中有谁和媒体关系紧密?
Tell me, who have a good connection with the media?
如果我想散播或者获得消息 谁能够帮忙?
If I want to pass or get some information, who can help me?
你去把他们三个人的手机没收
Please take away all their 3 mobiles.
好了 把手机给我吧
Come, give it to me.
这个案件属于机密案件
This is a high profile case.
不得和媒体透露相关情况
No one will talk to the media.
不管是验尸报告 法医检查报告
Autopsy or forensic report,
还是其他证据
whatever evidance we get, nothing should
在结案之前 都不得泄露
be leaked until this case is solved.
大家都听明白了吗?
Understand everyone?
案情不得泄露给媒体
Dont talk to the media
但是可以和我讨论
but can discuss with me.
长官
Sir,
我是拉克什·拉尼
I'm Rakesh Ranne.
你好 拉尼
Yes, Ranne.
长官 我觉得这个案件
Sir, I feel this case
没有办法结案
can never be solved.
我的意思是
I meant to say
在过去的三四年时间里
for past 3 to 4 years
在这条路上也发生过类似案件
back on the same road.
所有的案件都是未解之谜 而且案情相似
All of them was unsolve mistery and their files very close.
没有人明白是怎么回事 也不需要去证明什么
Nobody could understand anything. There was nothing to prove, too.
也不全是你想的那样 至少我现在能明白案情
Well one thing for sure, I can understand now.
你们在看什么呢?
What are you looking at?
鸨母 你好
Dear Madam.
- 对她们感兴趣吗? - 闭嘴
- Are you buying anyone? - Hey you shut up.
尼尔马拉 你要去哪里?
Where are you going Nirmala?
客人们都喜欢年轻貌美的女人
Customer needs young girls
而不是你这样的大妈
not aunty like you.
你们都过来吧
Come both of you.
别听他瞎说 你很漂亮
Do not listen to him, you look beautiful.
我知道
I know.
沙希 怎么了? 你看起来十分紧张
What is wrong Shashi? You look nervous.
沙希 把门打开
Shashi, open the door.
你在做什么?
What were you doing?
没什么
Just passing some time.
看看你都紧张成什么样了
See how worried you look.
这是你的新手机卡
Here is your new sim card.
把东西放屋里去
Keep the stuff inside
你要换手机号吗?
You changing you number?
你是律师吗? 问东问西的
Are you a lawyer? Every time asking me questions.
我要回村里呆几天
I will be going to my village for some days.
要是有人问起 你就告诉他们
If any one ask just inform them.
行了 你可以走了
Now, go away from here.
带我一起去吧
Take me along with you.
我要去那里办事 不是去旅游
I'm going for my work not to have fun.
我很快就回来
I will be back fast.
在我回来以前...
And untill then ...
不要和任何人提及此事
Do not tell anyone anything.
他为什么去西普利斯路?
What was he doing at Sipleas Road?
苏里 不要如此神秘
Suri,don't be so secretive.
给我们透露点有趣的消息吧
Tell us some intrested news about it.
没有什么 只是普通的车祸而已
Nothing much, it was just an accident.
可以把水递给我吗?
Can I have water please?
你见到索尼娅·卡普尔了吗?
Did you meet Sonia Kapoor?
她本人漂亮吗?
Does she look preety in real life?
太可惜了 他还年轻 不是吗?
So sad, he was very young right?
不应该死得这么早
He should not die.
每天都有成千上万的年轻人死于非命
Thousands of people die in young age everyday.
倒是没有人为他们感到忧伤
Nobody says anything then.
抱歉!
Sorry!
我的朋友 你在说什么呢?
My friend what are you talking?
没什么抱歉的 不是吗?
Why must you apologize to us?
她现在感觉如何?
How is she now?
比之前好很多
Better than last time.
我和心理医师安贾利·庞加比谈过
I have spoke to a psychiatric Anjali Punjabi.
嗯 她相当厉害
Yes she is quit good.
嗯 罗西尼也如此
Ya, I think the same for Roshini.
还需要其他什么吗?
Do you need anything?
不 谢谢
No, thanks.
转头
Turn back.
好的
Enough.
车的状况良好 刹车也没有问题
Car was in perfect condition, power breaks were good.
车撞向阶梯后 就直接冲到海里去了
While breaking the staircase the car straight went into the ocean.
看来他当时想救什么人
It looks more like he was trying to save someone.
但是当时马路上没有任何障碍物
But there was nothing on the road
而且他也不是酒后驾车
and he was not even drunk.
是的 长官 他的检查报告里面
Yes sir, there was nothing found
没有任何关于酒精中毒的信息
in his post mortem report of any toxication.
他的肺部积水过多 导致他溺水身亡
His lungs was full with water and he died of drawning.
长官
Sir.
我觉得这个案件没有办法结案 一切都说不通
I feel this going to be unsolve case, nothing is making sense.
走吧
Come on.
成千上万的来宾参加了宝莱坞影星
Thousands of people attended the burial
阿尔曼·卡普尔的葬礼
of Bollywood star Armaan Kapoor.
你好 我是弗拉尼 我住在这里附近
Hello,I'm Frani.I stay in this colony
今天我来拜访你们
and I come to welcome you guys today.
你太客气了 还送东西过来
It's ok, you should not have.
哎呀 亲爱的 不过是一点芝士蛋糕罢了
Oh darling,who don't like cheese cake?
需要我帮忙吗?
Do you need some help?
不 谢谢
No, thank you.
没有什么需要帮忙的 就是收拾东西罢了
I'm ok. Just just neede to do some unpacking.
如果需要帮忙的话 打电话给我就行了
If you need any help just call for me.
我是号码百事通
I have everyone's phone number:
木匠 电工 水管工
carpenter, electriction, plumber
这些人的号码我应有尽有...
and...
谢谢你
Thank you.
我能喝杯茶吗?
Can I have some tea?
哦 是的 当然 你请坐
Oh yes sure, please have a sit.
你的丈夫出门抓小偷时
Are you always alone at home
你常常一个人在家吗?
when your husband is chasing after thives?
你们结婚多久?
How many years have you been married?
十二年
12 years.
你需要加糖吗?
Do you take sugar?
是的 亲爱的 两勺糖
Yes dear, 2 tea spoons.
你好 卡伦
Hello Karen.
督查 你好
Hello inspector.
你好
Greetings.
这位是桑杰 他是阿尔曼的儿时好友
This is Sanjay, Armaan's childhood friend.
您请坐
Have a sit please.
谢谢
Thank you.
索尼娅 我们对你丈夫当晚的行踪不甚了解
Sonia,we still do not know where your husband when on that night,
也不知道他去那里做什么
or what was he doing on that road.
那车祸呢?
And accident?
我们也不明白为什么他的车会转弯坠入海里
And we also can't understand why his car turn and fall into the ocean.
索尼娅女士 我冒昧问一句
Madam Sonia,forgive me for asking
是的
Yes.
他是不是有什么困扰?
Was there any thing bothering him?
我的意思是 他是不是有什么心理压力
I meant was he having probleams.
督查 阿尔曼绝对不是自杀
Armaan did not kill himself Inspector!
他为什么自杀呢? 是你们没法结案 对吧?
Why will he kill himself? You guys cant solve the case, is it?
今天早上 我的会计师告诉我
Today morning, my accountant told me
事发当天 他给了阿尔曼 两百万卢比的现金
on that day he past Armaan Rs20 lakh cash.
为什么?
Why?
我是早上七点半把现金给他的
I gave him the cash at 7.30.
你之前怎么没把这件事情告诉索尼娅?
Why didn't you tell Sonia about this?
长官 我当时想告诉她
Sir, I tried to tell her but
但是看她那么难过 所以我没有开口
she was in a shock,that's why I could not talk to her.
以多大的面值给的?
What kind of notes was it?
上千的面值 当时是装在美洲豹牌的绿色包里
In thousands, it was a green colour PUMA bag.
我们没有找到你说的提包
We did not find such bag.
那天晚上 你是不是偷看了他的东西?
That night you peeked his stuff right?
快说!
Tell me!
行李有一些音乐器材 午餐饭盒
There were music system, lunch box
还有会计师给的提包
and a bag which was given by the accountant.
是红色的吧?
Red colour right?
不 长官 是绿色的包
No sir, it was green in colour
包里有什么? 你打开包看里面的东西了吗?
What was in that beg? Did you open and see it?
没有 长官 我不会不经过他的同意
No sir,I will never open his beg
擅自看他包里的东西
without his permission.
真的吗?
Really?
没错 长官
Really sir.
他对你提起过那个包的事情吗?
Did Mr Kapoor tell anything about the bag?
没有 长官
No sir.
他原来这么干过吗?
Have he done this before?
是的 有过两次.
Yes, 2 times.
一年前 阿尔曼先生让我
1 year back Mr. Armaan did ask me
把一百万卢比送到里多酒店
to deliver Rs 10 lakh to Hotel Lido...
这家酒店就位于发生车祸的那条马路
which is on the same road where his death tragic happen.
为什么?
Why?
我不知道 长官 他只是让我交给酒店前台
I do not know sir. I was just told to past it to the receptionist.
你们有个员工叫安纳德·穆鲁根吧?
You had a worker by the name of Anand Murugen?
穆鲁根...
Murugen...
他在你们酒店前台工作了四年
For 4 years he was you hotel receptionist.
是的 但是他辞职之后
But he has resign
我们就没有他的消息了
and after that we did not hear any news.
这是一个敲诈案件
It's extotion case.
如果当真如此 他肯定会对别人说起
If it's extotion im sure he would have talk to somebody.
就连他的妻子和关系好的朋友
Even his wife or any of his close friend
也不清楚这件事情
do not knows anything.
敲诈可能和他的死亡有所关联
Got blackmail any relevance to his death.
但是好像并非如此
By right it should not.
证据很多 可是没有办法联系起来
There are many evidence whithout the right answer.
今天早上 她的妻子要求做最终检验记录
And today his wife filed F.I.R.
这是她唯一可以做的事情
This was the only thing left for her to do.
出动所有警力 调查这起案件
Get all my police force to investigate for this Hero's case.
长官 如果找到那个前台服务员
Sir,If it is found that the desk clerk.
也许可以找到更多线索
Maybe you can find out more in detall.
争取早日破案
So find him faster.
是 长官
Yes,sir.
长官 我是沙希
Sir, Shashi speeking.
您多次给我打电话 发生什么事情?
What you want calling me so many times?
我早已更换电话号码 长官
Had to change my phone number sir.
最近发生一点麻烦
There is a problem going on.
那天晚上阿尔曼发生什么事情?
What happen that night with Armaan ?
我对此毫不知情 我当时并不在现场
I do not know anything. I was not even there.
不要狡辩 警察已经知道两百万卢比的事情
Don't lie, police knows about the Rs 20 lakh.
其他问题!
Other question please!
我们现在可以谈谈工作吗?
Shall we talk about work now?
你应该给我五百万
You was suppose to pay me Rs 50 lakh.
还差三百万
There is still Rs 30 Lakh balance.
他们为什么让孩子们跟着这些影视音乐跳舞?
why are they making the kids dance with such filmy songs?
他们就不能教授其他课程吗?
Can't they teach them anything else?
孩子们跳得很好看
The kids were looking great dancing.
罗西尼... 罗西尼
Roshini... Roshini
这个疯婆子是谁?
Who is this crazy woman?
你好 亲爱的
Hello, dear.
你好
Hello.
这是我的丈夫苏里 她是我们的邻居弗拉尼
This is my husband Suri and this is Frani our neighboor
她和她的哥哥维莱·莫里巡官住一起
and she stays with her brother Inspector Vilai Morri.
噢 我之前见过你的哥哥
oh, I have met you brother before.
可怜的人
Poor you dear.
你们准备回家吗?
Are you guys going home?
是的
Yes.
你还好吗 苏尔扬?
How are you Surjan?
我很好 怎么了?
I'm ok. Why?
没什么... 我实际上
No... I actcually wanted to meet you
我一直在等待机会
waiting for some time now.
我有个口信要带给你
I have a message for you.
口信? 谁的?
Message? From who?
你的儿子 卡伦
From you son, Karan.
他想我告诉你...
he wants me to tell you...
你在开什么玩笑?
What kind of joke is this?
不 不 听我说
No, no. Please listen to me.
卡伦想要我告诉你
Karan wants me to talk to you.
闭嘴! 闭嘴!
shut up! Just shut up!
我什么都不想听
I don't want to hear any more about it.
以后离我们远点 听明白了吗
You stay away from me hereafter, you understand?
给我滚远点
Stay the hell away from me.
我们走吧
Let's go.
他说 "告诉爸爸 我很好 不要担心"
He said "tell Dada that I'm fine and do not worry".
"告诉爸爸 我想和他谈谈"
"Tell Dada that I wish to talk to him."
她怎么知道卡伦以前叫你爸爸的?
How did she know that Karan use to call you Dada?
你之前说过 她到我们家 然后问东问西的
You told me once that she entered our house and was asking all kind of questions
但是我没有告诉她 关于卡伦的任何事情
But I did not inform her anything about Karan.
我不相信 有钱能使鬼推磨
I can't believe, for money sake people can act so weiredly.
如果她说的是事实呢?
How if she is telling the truth?
什么!
What!
如果她真的和卡伦说过话呢?
How if she really has spoken to Karan?
卡伦已经死了 罗西尼
Karen has past away, Roshini.
他不可能跟任何人说话
And he can't talk to anyone.
但是有些人可以通灵
But there are some people who can communicate with souls.
我在书上看到过
I have read in books.
你不应该相信这些 罗西尼
You should not believe in this kind of things, Roshini.
你应该成熟点
You are being a mature.
不要对我或者对你自己做这些
Please don't do this to me and to yourself.
就这一次 苏里 我们应该...
Just once, Suri. we should...
对不起 我不能再跟你继续这无稽的谈话
I'm sorry. I can't continue this unsensible talk with you.
这简直荒谬至极 我走了
It's too ridiculous. I'm going.
苏里! 就这一次 听听他吧  苏里!
Suri! please just for once, listen to him. Suri!
爸爸
Dada.
妈妈 我们能在附近玩一下吗?
Mama, can we go around?
当然可以
Ok, sure.
听着 卡伦! 不要走远 知道吗?
Listen Karan! Don't go so far, ok?
好的 当然
Ok, sure.
卡伦!
Karan!
苏里 快去找他
Suri, search for him.
卡伦!
Karan!
看来你十分渴望关爱
Looks like you are in need of love.
我可以让你所有的烦恼都消失
I can make all you worries diseapear.
去和别人说这些话吧
Please use this dialoge on some one else.
我是警察
I'm a cop.
在宵禁之前我还是可以做生意的
Got curfewed before I could even start my business.
没关系的 长官
It's doesn't matter,sir.
带上我一起吧
Please take with me.
你也可以抓我啊
You can also arrest me.
你已经堕落了 我何必再抓你
You are already in hell. Why must I arrest you?
我是堕落了 但是我知道通向天堂的路
I'm in hell, but I know the road to heaven.
从这里到里多酒店
From here straight into Hotel Lido.
在那里 每一个房间都是天堂
Over there in each room there is a heaven.
离这里很近的那个里多酒店吗?
Hotel Lido which is near here?
我和接待员的关系很好
I have a good connection with the receptionist.
他甚至都不会收我们房钱
He will not even charge us.
上车
Get in.
所有的男人都是一样的
All men are same.
你去里多几年了?
How many years you been going to Lido?
七年
7 years.
你知道穆鲁根吗?
Do you know Murugen?
安纳德·穆鲁根 他原来是那的一个接待员
Anand Murugen, he was the receptionist there.
为什么这么问?
Why?
我在找他
I'm searching for him.
我觉得没有人知道他在哪里
I feel nobody knows where he is.
大家都知道 他卖淫得病快死了
Everybody knows he is dying on the streets.
艾滋对我们来说可不是好事 长官
AIDS is not healty for our business, sir.
所以酒店经理炒了他
That's why the hotel manager fired him.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 就这些? - 就这些!
- That's it? - That's it!
你为什么赶我走 长官?
Why are you chasing me away sir?
我对你还有价值
I can be a good use for you.
如果我需要你 我会找你的 不过现在你走吧
If I need you, I will find you and now leave.
这么快就想我啦?
So fast you start missing me?
你叫什么?
What's you name?
洛奇
Rozy.
晚安 洛奇
Good night, Rozy.
你好 你知道安纳德·穆鲁根吗?
Hi. Do you know Anand Murugen?
噢 安纳德·穆鲁根 他住在那个房间
Oh, Anand Murugen. He is staying in that house.
安纳德·穆鲁根?
Anand Murugen?
长官 我是达夫拉
Sir, this is Devraj.
你说的没错穆鲁根得了艾滋病
You were right. Murugen have AIDS.
一年前 阿尔曼·卡普尔的会计给他一个包
1 year back, Armaan Kapoor's accountant did pass him a bag
让他给一个叫沙希的人
to be given to a guy name Shashi
谁是沙希?
Who is this Shashi?
他是拉皮条的 长官
He is a pimp, sir.
他在里多酒店提供色情买卖
He operates his business at Hotel Lido.
一年前 他给穆鲁根两千块让他把包送过去
1 year back, he paid Murugen Rs 2 thousand for delivering the bag.
穆鲁根说的是实话吗?
Is Murugen telling the truth?
警官 那个可怜的人就要死了 何必撒谎呢?
Sir, the poor man is dying. Why will he lie?
沙希在哪里?
where is Shashi?
他说他回老家做事去了
He told me he is going to his village for work.
做什么事?
What work?
他为什么要告诉我?
Why did he inform me what work?
他什么时候回来?
When is he coming back?
我不知道
I do not know.
仔细听好我的话
Listen very carefully what I'm going to say now.
沙希现在有麻烦
Shashi is in trouble.
如果你想帮他 那你最好告诉我他在哪
If you want to help him, better tell me where he is now.
警官 我真的不知道
sir, I really do not know.
那他有提过阿尔曼·卡普尔吗?
Did he ever mention anything about Armaan Kapoor?
沙希在哪里?
where is Shashi?
我不知道
I do not know.
他已经失踪有些时日了
It's been few days he is missing.
有人说他回老家了
someone told me that he went back to his village.
老家在哪里?
Village means?
就是把奶牛当车使的地方
Village means where the cows are used as cars that is a Village.
你是一个优秀的喜剧演员
You are a good comedian.
但是很不幸 我不觉得这好笑
But you are unlucky that I don't find it hillirious.
我给你两个选择
I give you 2 choices.
第一 你带我们去沙希那里
First choice, you take us to shashi's place.
第二 直接去警察局
Second choice, straight to police station.
给你一分钟
One minute.
你凭什么逮捕我?
On what reason will you arrest me ?
达夫拉 她的确是一个好的喜剧演员
Devraj, she is in deed a good comedian.
我开始觉得有趣了
I'm begining to find it funny now.
克斯汀娜 跟着 带上我的日记
Cristina, go up and get my diary.
长官 这是达夫拉 沙希不在他老家
Sir, this is Devraj. Shashi is not at his village.
我就知道 他不会在那里
I knew, he will not be there.
没关系 你回来吧
It's ok. You should come back
然后告诉警察派人看着他家
and inform the police there to keep an eye on his family.
不管有什么代价 我们都得找到他
What ever it takes, we must find this man
是的 长官
Yes sir.
先生 我要这味药
Sir, I need this medicine.
卡伦从小就喜欢玩水
Karan likes to play in water since a baby.
我还记得
I still remember.
在我准备跟他放水洗澡时
When I used to prepare the tub for his bath,
他总是非常开心
he used to be so happy.
他总是朝我吐水
He used to throw water on me from his mouth,
然后开怀大笑
and then he will giggle so much.
他喜欢呆在水里
He liked to stay in the water.
他真的有可能是溺水身亡的吗?
Was it nesecary he die drowning?
对父母来说 没有什么比失去孩子更痛苦
For parents, to lost their child is the most painfull thing ever.
我可以理解
I can understand.
有时天有不测风云
Sometimes in life, this happens.
老天会带走我们生命里最珍贵的人
The most precious people in our life are taken away
但是我们还是得继续活下去 知道吗?
but still we have to live. ok?
有点耐心 罗西尼
Be patient, Roshini.
我很有信心
I have full confidence.
使用合适的药物 你就会远离这些烦忧
With proper medication, you will be able to get out of this.
毕竟你还有你的丈夫的支持
After all, you also have you husband's support.
那时 和卡伦在一起 差点让我失去了苏里
At that moment, together with Karan I have also lost Suri.
其实苏里比我更需要你的帮助
The truth is actually Suri needs your help more then me.
他的所思所感
What he is thinking or feeling,
从不与人分享
he never talks about it.
他从不跟我说 甚至谈起卡伦
He never spoke to me even regarding Karan.
从不
Never.
你觉得 他对这件事情不够在意吗?
Do you feel that he do not care about this thing?
他在意
He cares.
如果他不在意的话 他晚上不会睡不好的
If he did not, he will not be able to sleep at night.
# 我的悲伤痛苦 你的沉默不语 #
# 错怪时间无情 可惜事实已经注定 #
# 一次又一次的打击 痛苦长存心中 #
# 为何内心依旧想要诉说 #
# 继续生活 #
# 内心告诉我们 继续生活 #
# 我的旅伴 我的灵魂伴侣 #
# 走近一点 继续生活 #
# 即便生活充满痛苦 #
# 但是生活充满慰藉 #
# 我属于你 你属于我 #
# 我们希望 感情永远不会褪色 #
# 为何这条路带我走向你的灭亡 #
# 我们为何如此相遇 #
# 打开大门 让一切随风而去 #
# 让我们大声呼喊 擦干眼泪 #
# 继续生活 #
# 内心告诉我们 继续生活 #
# 我的旅伴 我的灵魂伴侣 #
# 走近一点 继续生活 #
# 让痛苦的愁云随风消逝 #
# 让灿烂的生命绽放每一天 #
# 让过去成为过去 #
# 倾听内心的声音 #
# 继续生活 #
# 内心告诉我们 继续生活 #
# 我的旅伴 我的灵魂伴侣 #
# 走近一点 继续生活 #
长官 这个人是沙希最重要的人
sir the guy is Shashi's most important man.
穿着黄上衣 正朝你走来
He's wearing yellow shirt, walking towards you.
嗨 塔姆尔
Hey, Tamoor.
你好 长官
Yes, sir.
你叫塔姆尔 对吧?
Your name is Tamoor, right?
你是干什么的?
What do you do?
我是一个乞丐 长官
I'm a begger, sir.
我很穷 甚至没有钱买吃的
I'm very poor, even no money to eat.
你在哪里跟我打电话? 请告诉我
Where are you talking me? Tell me, please.
快说!
Talk!
他什么都没说 长官
He is not talking, sir.
长官 我对沙希在哪里一无所知
Sir, I do not know anything where is Shashi.
我以我妈妈的名义起誓 我什么都不知道
I swear upon my mother. I don't know anything.
闭嘴! 闭嘴！
shut up! shut up！
这位长官是特别派来的警官
This sir is ancounter specialist.
两天内 他在同一个地方杀了四个人
2 days back, he killed 4 guys in this same cell,
你知道吗?
you understand?
现在快说 说!
Now talk, talk!
长官 我发誓 我真的不知道
Sir, I swear I really do not know.
如果你接到沙希的电话 你会怎么做?
If you receive Shashi's call, what will you do?
我会第一时间通知你
I will call you immediatly.
如果你不呢?
If you don't?
那就打断我的腿
Sir, chop my legs if I don't.
那好 你可以走了
Ok, you can go.
真的吗?
Truly?
走 快走
Go. Get going.
沙希对你根本不好
shashi don't treat you well.
他把你当狗使唤
He treats you like a dog.
你最好跟长官说实话
It's better you tell the truth to sir.
那样对你才是最安全的 知道吗?
And better save your life, do you understand?
潘德伊 你知道我的
Phandey, you know about me.
我不是在帮沙希
I'm not helping Shashi,
或说充当英雄
or trying to be a hero.
我只是想离所有人都远点
I just want to be away from everyone.
他在干大票
He is playing a big game.
沙希从阿尔曼·卡普尔那里拿了两百万
Shashi took Rs 20 lakh from Armaan Kapoor.
他现在肯定没剩多少了
He can't be saved now.
总有一天他会被抓到的
One day for sure, he will be cought.
您拨打的电话是空号
The number you calling is not valid.
塔姆尔 请给我点水
Tamoor, please give me water.
沙希 你最好弄清楚
Shashi, you better get this clear.
一天之内 不要跟我打上十次电话
Do not call me 10 times in a day.
我告诉过你 你明天就可以拿到钱了
I told you, you will get your money tomorrow.
明天早上 八点见面
I will see you at 8 in the morning.
如果你还想要钱 就别再跟我打电话了
If you need the money, don't you dare call me again.
沙希来过这里吗?
Did Shashi come here?
不 不 长官 他没有来过这里
No, no. Sir, he did not.
我知道 你会来找我的
I knew it that you will find me.
为什么?
why?
因为所有人都为我神魂颠倒
Becouse people get attracted with me.
你又如何能幸免!
How will you save yourself!
你关于穆鲁根的话都是对的
Your information were right regarding Murugen.
我为什么要骗你...
Why will I lie...
这里的人都不帮助警察
The people over here do not help police.
因为警察不帮助我们这些人
Becouse police do not help people like us.
法律对所有人都是公平的
Law is fair to all.
你真的很好笑 长官
You are very hilirious, sir.
你去哪里?
Where are you going?
你觉得呢 长官?
Where do you think, sir?
我不是来照顾你生意的
I did not come with you for this.
那你为什么跟着我?
So then why did you follow me?
你为什么撒谎 长官?
Why are you lying, sir?
我知道你很空虚寂寞
I know you are very lonely.
你心里装的不再是你的妻子
Your heart is not with you wife anymore.
为什么?
why?
我不是来跟你玩游戏的
I'm not here to play game with you.
你认识沙希吗?
Do you know Shashi?
沙希 我倒希望不认识他
Shashi, I don't wish to know him.
他可不是个好人
He is not a good guy.
你帮他做事吗?
Do you work for him?
我是他的头牌
I'm one of his best girls.
他现在在哪里？
Where is he now?
我不知道
I don't know.
我在找他
I'm searching him.
你会帮我吗?
Will you help me?
让你的人代替我做事
Ask your men to replace my work
我就代替他们帮你
and I will replace them
做一次警察
as a policewoman.
如果你想的话 我可以帮你
If you want, I can help you.
真的吗?
Really?
你能帮我什么?
What can you do for me?
睁大你的眼睛看清楚
Keep your gorgeous eye vision clear.
我不知道沙希在哪里
I do not know where is Shashi.
他醉倒在哪个女人的怀里
In which womans arms is he lying down drunk,
但是不久他就会被淹死
but how long will he be drown.
那时候就快到了 他得游上岸
The time will come, he need to swim to the shore.
沙希惹上大麻烦了 上百万的麻烦
Shashi is involve in a big trouble, in Rs lakhs.
告诉警察 让他去坐牢
Tell the cops and get him arrest.
现在是他补偿我的时候了
Now, it's time he pay me back.
我为他无恶不作
I did worst things for him.
他从来不为你做点什么
He will never do anything for you.
必须这么做 必须这么做
Got to do it, got to do it.
我有权利
I have the rights.
我想问你点事
I would like to ask you something.
别喝了 我有重要的事想跟你谈
Stop drinking. I need to talk to you something important.
做这个工作就得喝酒 你懂吗?
To be in this work, I need to drink, you understand?
说吧
Tell me.
尼尔马拉
Nirmala.
如果我有钱了
If I become rich,
你会跟我结婚吗?
will you marry with me?
你让警察打昏了头了吧?
Police hit on your head, is it?
回答我
Answer me.
你会答应我吗
Will you follow me?
把你那些无聊的想法掏出来喂狗 听懂了吗?
Take out your thoughts from your heart and feed it to the dogs, you get it?
我是一个妓女 你最好离我远点
I'm a prostitute and better you stay away from me, it will be better for you
你要是想好好活着
If you wanna stay alive,
就别参与到沙希的破事里面
don't be involve with Shahsi's matter.
妈妈 我们能到附近玩一下吗?
Mama, can we go around?
是的 当然
Yes, sure.
卡伦!
Karen!
不要走
Do not need to go any way.
爸爸
Dada.
- 我们来玩国际象棋 - 是的 当然
- Let's play Checkers. - Ok, sure.
谁要红棋?
Who wants red?
- 我 ... - 我
- I ... - I
妈妈 我们能到附近玩一下吗?
Mama, can we go around?
是的 当然
Yes, sure.
卡伦 等一下 我跟你们一起去
Karen, wait. I will come along.
我是卡伦·西卡瓦特
I am Karen shikawat.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
你能不能帮我 去找我的爸爸妈妈?
Can you please help me to to call my mamy and dada?
我要跟他们谈谈
I need to talk to them.
他们是罗西尼和苏尔扬
Their name is Roshini and Surjan.
请你通知他们 我很想和他们讲话
Please inform them, I want to talk to them.
亲爱的 注意力集中
Concentrate, my dear.
我来是想跟卡伦谈话
I have come here to talk to Karen.
您能帮我联系到卡伦吗?
Can you make me reach to Karen?
妈妈 你好 我就在你的旁边
Hello, mama. I'm here next to you.
能跟你讲话 我很高兴
I'm happy. I'm able to talk to you.
谢谢 妈妈
Thank you, mama.
求你让爸爸也来跟我讲话
Please tell Dada to also talk to me.
我知道你们因为我都很难过
I know both of you are sad becouse of me.
我一直与你们同在
I'm always with you all.
妈妈 请你不要难过
Mom,please don't be sad.
我想要看到你一直像现在这样笑
I want to see you always smiling like this.
我知道你很空虚寂寞
I know you are very lonely.
你心里装的不再是你的妻子
Heart is no more with your wife.
我知道 你会来找我的
I knew it that you will come to find me.
因为所有人都为我神魂颠倒
Everyone gets attracted with my personality.
你又如何能幸免!
How can you stay away from me!
我不是来跟你玩游戏的
I did not come here to play game with you.
那你为什么要来?
Then why are you here?
你认识沙希吗?
Do you know who is Shashi?
睁大你的眼睛看清楚
Keep your gorgeous eye vision clear.
我不知道沙希在哪里
I do not know where is Shashi.
他醉倒在哪个女人的怀里
In which woman arms is he lying down drunk.
怎么了?
What happen?
找到一具被系上石头 扔到海里的尸体
Found a body tied with a rock and thrown in to the sea.
但是人能溺水多久呢 警官
But how long will somebody stay drown, sir.
尸体在水里沉了四天
For 4 days, the body stayed under water.
总归要游回岸上来的
There will be a time that he have to swim and come shore.
- 送去验尸了吗? - 没有 长官
- Have you send the boby for post mortem? - No, sir.
还在等人来认领
Still waiting to identify the body.
你说什么?
What you said?
长官 我们发现一具尸体
Sir, we found a death body.
杀手把石头系在尸体上
Killer tied the body with a rock.
四天之前发生的
This happen 4 days back.
达夫拉
Devraj.
把沙希的照片发给所有的停尸间和医院
Send Shashi's picture to all the mortuaries and hospitals.
现在就去
Now.
昨天晚上八点半 被来福枪击中头部
Around 8.30 pm yesterday, he was shot at his head with a rifle.
凶手距离他至少300米左右
The murderer was at least 300 meters away from he.
现在我们知道凶手用的是来福枪
We now know that the murderer used the rifle.
应该是他 长官
just him,sir.
我们在他的口袋里找到他的房间钥匙
We found his room keys from his pocket.
他以克里斯纳·奈尔的名字入住金夜旅馆
He was staying at Hotel Golden Nights, registerd as Krisna Nair.
包里没有什么东西
There was nothing much in his beg.
仅有衣服 甚至连能识别的细节都没有
Just cloths,not even any identification details.
为什么这么重?
Why is it heavy?
为什么都这么难过?
Why is evey one very sad?
沙希死了
Shashi is dead.
什么?
What?
你在胡说什么?
What nonsense are you talking?
我说的是真的 他死了
I'm telling the truth, he is dead.
昨天在游乐园
Yesterday at the fun fair.
被人一枪爆头了
Being a shot to the head.
他去那里做什么?
But what was he doing there?
沙希 仔细听我说
Shashi, listen to me carefull.
不要一天打十次电话
Stop calling me 10 times in a day.
照我说的做 你明天就会拿到钱
I told right, you will get the money tomorrow.
明天早上八点 在游乐园等我
Just be at the funfair tomorrow at 8.
你是律师吗? 每次都问东问西的!
Are you a lawyer? Everytime you like to ask questions!
你昨天真的遇到他了吗?
Really you met him last night?
我还以为你在开玩笑
I was thinking you were just kidding.
他在干一场大票
He is playing a big game.
沙希从阿尔曼·卡普尔那里拿了二百万卢比
Shashi took Rs 20 lakh from Armaan kapoor.
你看没看到沙希有绿色的包?
Did you see any green colour beg with Shashi?
我不想回去 塔姆尔
I don't want to go, Temoor.
对不起 马里卡 大姐让你回去
Sorry Malika, madam is calling you back.
- 沙希已经把我赎出来了 - 跟我们走
- Shashi has paid for my freedom. - Let's go.
沙希 大哥
Shashi. Brother.
进来吧 长官 她失血过多
Come in, sir. She is badly bleeding.
沙希为什么不把她送到医院?
Shahsi. Why you don't take her to hospital?
医生来了也没用
No hospital doctor did something in here.
你如果把这件事情告诉别人 你就惹麻烦了
You will be in trouble if you tell anybody about this,
懂不懂?
you understand?
至少沙希死前帮过我的忙
At last before dying, Shashi has done a favour for me.
因为是现金 所以我们要报给所得税部门
We had to report to the income tax department as it was cash money.
你们要付偿还额
You have to apply for the refund.
阿尔曼是怎么认识沙希的?
How did Armaan know shashi?
现在我还无法回答你
At this moment, I do not have any answers for you question.
为什么敲诈阿尔曼?
Why was blackmailing Armaan?
索尼娅 他跟你说了他不知道
Sonia, he is telling right that he does not know.
有可能
Inspecting it is possiable.
阿尔曼通过沙希买女孩子
Armaan was buying girls through shashi.
索尼娅 别说了
Sonia, please.
我想知道事实
I want to know the truth.
我不确定 但是有可能
I'm not that sure, but yes, it can be possiable.
你好 我是沙希的朋友
Hello, I'm Shashi's friend.
不好意思
Execuse me.
你是谁?
Who is this?
我刚刚告诉你了 我是谁
I just told you that who am I.
你还记得沙希吧?
You still remember Shashi right?
你让他在游乐园和你碰面
You called him for the meething at the funfair.
然后你把他杀了
And then you killed him.
听着 我在参加一个重要会议 待会回你电话
Listen here, I'm in an important meething now, I will call you back.
不 不 不 不用麻烦你了
No, no, no. Why are you taking the efford?
一小时后打给你
I will call you back after an hour.
一定要接! 知道吗?
Pick my call! OK?
不然你会付出代价的!
If not, you will pay for it!
好的
Ok.
搞定他了 中大奖了
I have got him, strike lottery.
真没想到 你也有变精明的一天 塔姆尔
Nobody knew that you also will turn to be smart, Tamoor.
是的 说吧
Yes,talk.
我要五百万卢比
Yes, I want Rs 50 lakh.
什么? 为什么?
What? For what?
为了保住你的秘密
To keep you secret save.
什么秘密? 别把我惹恼了
What secret? Look, do not make me angry.
好吧 如果你不跟我合作 警察就会找上门的
Ok, fine. If you don't corporate with me, then the police will.
我会把沙希的手机卡和DVD光盘交给警察
I will past shahsi's sim card and DVD to the police.
我知道那个女孩的一切
I know everything about the girl.
我惹上麻烦了 爸爸
I'm in trouble, dad.
- 大麻烦 - 怎么了?
- I'm in a big trouble. - What happen?
我和阿尔曼
Me and Armaan.
有些人勒索我们
There are some people blackmailing us.
什么?
What?
哪些人?
Which people?
你还记得尼卡尔发生的意外吗?
Do you still remember Nikael's accident?
是的
Yes.
他不是从孟买珠湖的房子上摔下来的
He did not fall from our bungalow at Juhu.
我撒谎了
I lied to you.
他在我们开车的时候摔了下去
He fell from the car while we were driving.
那是一个意外 爸爸
It was an accident, dad.
你今天怎么回来这么早?
How come you are back early today?
怎么 不想我回来吗
how,don't you want me to come back?
苏里
Suri.
你还回去工作吗
Are you going back to work?
不
No.
那我们出去吧
If in that case, let's go out somewhere.
去哪里?
Where?
我们去看电影 顺便在外面吃饭吧
Let's watch a movie and also have dinner out today.
求你了 苏里! 去吧
Please, suri! Let's go.
我情不自禁要笑 你觉得电影怎么样?
I could not stop laughing, how did you find the movie?
我在看你
I was watching you.
看到你高兴 我也高兴
Felt good seing you happy.
谢谢 罗西尼
Thank you, Roshini.
应该多见见庞加比医生
Should keep on meeting Dr Punjabi.
我知道你不容易
I know it's not easy for you.
我看得出来你改变一些
But I can see the differance in you.
嗨 罗西尼阿姨
Hi, Roshini aunty.
萨马尔
Samar.
你们来孟买了
You guys here in Mumbai.
我的表兄下周结婚
My cousion is getting married next week.
我原想打你电话的
I wanted to call you,
萨马尔也想见见你们
and Samar wanted to meet you guys too.
有空一定要到我家来
If you get some time, do come to my place.
一起吃晚饭
Have dinner with us.
好的 为什么不呢?
Sure, why not?
周五怎么样?
Why not on friday?
周五我要加班
I'm working late on fridays.
周六呢?
Why not on saturday then?
我这个周末都很忙
I'm going to be busy the whole week.
有个新案子 最近都腾不出空来
It's a new case. That's why I don't get free time nowadays.
没事 警察总是忙得很
It's ok, police guys are always busy.
你怎么回事?
How was you behaving?
他们肯定不好受
I'm sure they felt very bad.
我们是朋友 苏里
They are our friends, Suri.
是的 但是哪里规定了我要和他们见面
Ya, but where is it written that I have to meet them.
你想见的话 我不会拦你
You meet them. I did not stop you.
每次看到萨马尔...
Whenever I look at Samar...
他只是个孩子 苏里
He is a kid, Suri.
无论发生了什么 都不是他的错
Whatever happen was not his fault.
我知道
I know that.
是我的错
It was my mistake.
那是一个意外 苏里
It was an accident, Suri.
不是意外 是我的疏忽
That was not an accident. That was my negligence.
我的错
Mine.
我应该看着他的 但是我却在睡觉
I should have kept my eyes on him, but I slept.
我也在睡觉
I slept too.
我们不知道孩子们会那样
We did not know that the kids will be doing such thing.
苏里不要责怪你自己
Please suri, don't blame yourselve.
说起来容易 罗西尼
It's easy to say such words, Roshini.
每次看你的双眼 我只看得到真相
Whenever I look into your eyes, I can only see this truth.
我从未那样想
But I never thought like this.
我从未往那方面想过
and I never even think in such way
但是我每天都这样想
But I think about it everyday.
不要那样
Don't think in such way.
你不能那样想 我们进去吧
You cant think like this lets go in.
我还要工作
No. I got work to do.
求你了 苏里
Please, Suri.
苏里
Suri.
# 你的内心 痛苦不已 #
# 你不曾理解所有 #
# 你抛弃身边的心爱之人 #
# 只剩下你孤身一人 #
# 我心已倦 不愿与你分开 #
# 不知为何 #
# 不知怎样 #
# 剑拔弩张 #
# 苦苦挣扎 #
# 苦苦追寻 #
# 苦苦挣扎 苦苦追寻 #
# 我在你的方向 #
# 我是谜题 #
# 我是传说 #
# 不曾结束 #
# 走近观察 你便会知晓 #
# 距离依旧 命中注定 #
# 我心已倦 不愿与你分开 #
# 不曾解开的谜题 #
# 你是不解之谜 #
# 无人知晓这个秘密 #
# 你究竟与何人为友 #
# 微笑着从大千世界中隐退 #
# 日日夜夜 不曾安眠 #
# 闭上双眼 已有多时 #
# 内心平静 已有多时 #
# 我心已倦 不愿与你分开 #
你从不回家 长官
Don't you ever go home, sir.
你晚上也从未睡着
And you cant even sleep at night.
为什么?
Why?
我想问你点事
I wanted to ask you something.
如果没时间 我等会再来
If no time, I'll come back later.
看他们怎么盯着我了么
See how there are staring at me.
他们一定在想 你今天和我一起
They must be thinking, today you are being with me.
有什么区别?
What's the differance?
走吧 我带你去个地方
Lets go. I will take you to such a place.
没有人能看到我们
where no body can see us.
这是哪里?
Where are we?
这是我的地盘
This is my place.
没有人来过这里
Nobody comes here,
如果你想找我
if you cant find me anyway.
在这里就能找到我
You will find me here.
这里多安宁 是吧?
How peaceful is here right?
为什么如此难过?
Why are you so sad?
谁说我难过了?
Who said that im sad?
不想说的话 就不用说
我们谈点别的吧
Let's talk something else.
你的案子调查的如何?
Whats happening with your case investigation?
我听说沙希死了
I heard Shashi dead.
我不知道我在找什么
I don't know what Im seaching for.
我走的每条路 只会让我更加迷失
Each road that I take, only makes me get more lost.
感觉前方的答案都是正确的
Feels like all the answers are right in front of me,
但是我还是不能解决问题
but I still cant solve it.
能问你个问题吗?
Can I ask you a question?
问吧
Ask me.
沙希把你介绍给哪些有钱人了吗?
Did Shashi introduced you with any rich guy?
你是指阿尔曼·卡普尔
You meant Armaan Kapoor.
为什么不直接点的问我 长官?
Why don't you ask me straight away sir?
我不会感到被冒犯的
I won't get offended.
这是我的工作
This is my job.
我从未和他出去过
I have never gone out with him.
但是他的一个朋友是我的顾客
But one of his friend was my customer,
有一次阿尔曼·卡普尔和他一起来了
and there was once Armaan Kapoor come with him.
为什么没有告诉我这个?
Why you did not tell me this?
你没有问过
You never ask.
什么时候遇到他的?
When did you meet him?
三年前
3 years back.
那时他还不出名
At that time he was not famous.
尼卡尔还带来另一个朋友
Nikhal also brought one of his other friend.
还有一个人
There was another man with him.
我们一起兜风
We went for a drive.
就这样
That's all.
第三个人
The third man.
是叫桑杰·基格里沃吗?
Was his name Sanjay Gigriwal?
我不知道他叫什么
I do not know his name.
但是我要是再见到他 肯定能认出他来
But once I look at him, I will be able to identify.
为什么你要过这样的生活 洛奇?
Why are you in this kind of life, Rozy?
那个地方不适合你
This place does not suit you.
我在等你
I was waiting for you.
你会来吗?
Will you come here?
带我离开
And take me away from here.
如果你想离开的话 告诉我一声就好
If you want to be out, just tell me.
我会立刻带你离开
I will right away take you out now.
我知道 但是现在不行
I know that, but not this fast.
我的债务尚未还清
I still have some debts to pay.
容我先把债还了吧?
Can I clear it first?
还用问吗 长官
What else, sir.
也许以后 我能帮上你的忙
Maybe one day, I can be help for you.
我对此深信不疑 长官
I have to believe this, sir.
你和其他人截然不同
You are not same like the other guys.
据我判断
From my judgment,
你的归宿应在别处
your place belongs some where else.
是吗?
Really?
你关心他人
You know, you care for others.
也不会趁人之危
And don't even take advantage of others,
现如今这种人已经不多了
and you can't find this kind of people nowadays.
三年前我的一位朋友
Three years back, one of my friend
和嫖客一起离开后
went out with some guys,
便再也杳无音讯
and she did not return.
没人知道她现在身在何方
Nobody knows where she is,
在世与否
whether is she still alive or dead.
根本没人会关心
No one cares.
很值得深思 对吗 长官?
Something to think about. Right, sir?
一个女孩失踪了 却无人问津
A girl goes missing any no one even bother asking.
你报案了吗?
Did you do a police report?
你在说什么 先生?
What are you talking, sir?
看样子我得给你普及一下法律知识
Looks like I have to teach you the law.
卖淫是违法的
Being a prostitute is against the law.
像我们这样的人不计其数 长官
You can't even count people like us, sir.
世间从未有过她们存在的痕迹
When they don't event appear for others,
又怎么会人间蒸发呢?
how can they go missing?
你好 我是西卡瓦特警长
Greetings, I'm inspector Shekawat.
我来拜访尼卡尔·德西潘迪
I'm here to meet Nikhal Deshpandy.
他想来拜访尼卡尔
He wants to meet Nikhal.
尼卡尔 有人来拜访你了
Nikhal, see. You have a guest.
医生说 他现在的理解能力有所欠缺
Doctor said he can't really understand much now.
他清楚得很 我知道!
He understands. I know it!
事故发生之后 他就失语了
After the accident, he never speak.
数据表明 利润增长了百分之八
The profit recorded went by eight percent,
这个趋势表明这个部分有稳定增长
and this trend indicates that there's a substantial growth in this sector,
根据...
and according to...
你好 请稍等
Hello, hold on please.
伙计们 我去处理一些急事... 请继续
Guys, I have some difficulties, so... Please continue.
好的 正如我所说 根据...
Ok, as I'm saying, according to the...
我要和你见面
I want to meet you.
准备好现金了吗?
Have you arrange the cash?
你拿我的话当耳旁风吗?
Didn't you hear what I was telling you?
我要当面见你!
I want to meet you!
嘿 你以为我是傻子吗?
Hey, do you think I'm stupid?
你以为你对沙希所做的事情 我一无所知吗?
You think I don't know what you did to Shahsi?
我没有杀他!
I did not kill him!
事实上 我当时就拿着包 在那里等他
In fact, I was there with the bag waiting for him.
这么多年来 我从未断了他的财路
For all this years, I have been giving him money,
为何现在才动手?
and now why must I kill him?
我随时都能取你的小命 明白吗?
I can kill you whenever I want, do you understand?
这么做 对你有什么好处呢?
But what is the benefit?
好好想想吧
Think again.
我愿意带着钱来跟你见面
I'm willing to meet you with the money.
时间和地点由你决定
The place and time you decide.
怎么把灯关了?
Why is the lights off?
进来吧 达夫拉 进来
Come in, Devraj. Come in.
罗西尼
Roshini.
我不知道她在哪里
I don't know where is she.
要喝点什么吗?
Would you like to have a drink?
好的
Ok, sure.
威士忌可以吗
Whisky,OK?
加苏打水还是水
With soda water or water?
加水
water.
加冰吗
Add ice?
好的
OK.
抱歉 达夫拉
Sorry, Devraj.
我想她忘记 你要过来吃晚饭了
I think she forgot that you are coming for dinner.
她和朋友去看电影了
She has gone to watch a movie with her friend.
没关系 长官
It's ok, sir.
喂 苏里 你好吗?
Hello Suri, how are you?
抱歉 米拉 打扰你看电影了
Sorry, Meera. I'm disturbing your movie.
我想让罗西尼接电话
Accually I want to talk to Roshini.
她的电话打不通
I can't get throug her mobile.
什么电影?
Which movie?
罗西尼没有和我在一起
Roshini is not with me.
没事吧?
Is everything ok?
没事 没事 抱歉 她可能去了别的地方
Yes, yes, ok. I'm sorry she went somewhere else.
我弄错了 对不起
I made a mistake, sorry.
达夫拉
Devraj.
你知道比鲁·莫里在哪里吗?
Do you know where Bilu Morri stays?
第二街区的一楼
At Block 2, Ground floor.
怎么了 长官?
What happened, sir?
罗西尼在哪里?
Where is Roshini?
她在里面 请稍等一下
She is inside, please wait.
长官 你不能进去
我早就让你滚的远远的 对吧?
I told you right to stay away, did I?
你疯了吗?
Are you crazy?
你在这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
卡伦已经死了 无法跟你进行交流
Karen has died and he can't talk to you anymore.
我了解你的愤怒 你痛不欲生
I understand you anger. you have pain in your heart.
你最好闭嘴
You better be quit.
如果你真的能和卡伦交谈
If you really can talk to Karen,
那就告诉他 我要见他 他在哪里?
then call him I want to see him. Where is he?
我做不到
I can't do that.
只有还在世间徘徊的灵魂
Only those souls which are around in this world
才能现出人形
can transform into human.
但是卡伦已经去了另一个世界
But Karen had no problem to travel from this world to theirs.
他走得很安详
He went peacefully.
是的 他走得很安详
Yeah, right. He went peacefully.
他八岁就溺水而死
He died drowning in the age of 8 years old.
怎么可能走得安详?
How can that be peacefull?
这个世间无法解释的事情很多
In this world there are alots kind of situation that can't be explain.
我并未选择这种宿命
I did not choose this life.
一切都是上天注定
This life choose me.
过来 我们走吧!
Come, lets go!
听我说 苏里
Listen to me, Suri.
首先你要排解痛苦 否则你就会备受折磨
Resolve you pain first, if not you will suffer.
我丈夫去世时 我痛不欲生
When my husband died I went through a lot of pain
那也是我第一次开始和魂灵对话
and then for the first time the souls started talking to me.
走吧
Let's go.
魂灵会被你我这样深处痛苦中的人们所吸引
Those souls will get attracted to people like us who are in pain
他们会觉得我们是同类
and they feels like we are also like them.
放开我
Let me go.
你居然跟我撒谎? 你隐瞒了事实
You lied to me? You hide the truth.
我要怎么告诉你事实! 你连家都不回!
How can I tell you the truth! Are you even at home!
不要转移话题 罗西尼
Don't change the topic Roshini.
你居然相信这些虚无缥缈的东西
You really believe in this kind of things.
你是受过教育的人
You are such an educated person,
以前还是科学老师
used to teach science.
好好想想 罗西尼 动动脑子
Just think, Roshini, use you brain.
你怎么能对这些胡言乱语深信不疑呢?
How could you believe in all this kind of nonsense?
我不知道还有谁能相信
I do not know who to believe,
但是我知道 她能告诉我
but I just know that she told me
一些只有卡伦知晓的事情
such things that only Karen knew it.
我乐在其中
I'm happy doing this.
你怎么就不能理解呢?
Why don't you understand?
卡伦很想和你交谈!
Karen wants to talk to you!
你疯了
You have become crazy.
你需要治疗
You need treatment.
我不需要治疗 只想跟你好好谈谈
I do not need any treatment but need to talk to you.
你能跟我交心吗?
Can you talk to me?
哪怕就陪我一个晚上?
Can you once stay one night with me?
我们能像夫妻一般亲密无间
Can we once stay like married couple
而不是像陌生人一般吗?
then being like strangers?
我先告辞了 长官
I see you later, sir.
听着
Listen.
你和他一起工作 对吗?
You work with him, right?
你也总是整晚不回家吗?
You also stay whole night out from your family?
你的妻子乐意你这么做吗?
Is your wife happy with this?
苏里 你要去哪里?
Where do you go Suri?
我又何曾问过你一句?
Have I ever ask you before?
晚上你都和谁在一起?
Who are you with at nights?
我知道你根本没有在工作
I know you are not doing your work.
我知道你跟人有约
I know you are meeting someone else.
但是不论你身在何方 在做什么
But where ever you go ,what ever you do,
你都乐在其中
you spent your time and feel happy with it.
为什么我就不能做点喜欢的事情
Then why I can't do something
来聊以自娱呢?
that I'm happy with?
回头见 长官
I see you later, sir.
夫妻之间吵架再正常不过了
It's commen for husband and wife to have argue.
你和苏里近来经历太多
You and Suri has gone throught so much recently.
多给彼此一点时间
Give some time.
一切都会好起来的
Everything will be fine.
我想不会
I don't think so.
你们为什么不再要一个孩子呢?
Why don't you try to have another child?
苏里不想要
Suri don't want it.
我以前跟他提过
I did talk to him once.
他连听都不想听
He doesn't want to even listen.
我觉得他有外遇了
I think he is having affair.
什么?
What?
不 不可能
No, it's impossible.
罗西尼 我们说的是苏里吗?
Roshini, we are talking about Suri here?
我就此事询问过他
I did ask him.
他并未否认
and he did not even deny it.
你怎么会过来?
How come you are here?
我想见你
I wanted to meet you.
你爱上我了吗 长官?
Have you fallen in love with me, sir?
开玩笑的
I was just kidding.
你有事要问我吗?
So what, would you like to ask me now?
长官 你没事吧?
Sir, are you ok?
我精疲力尽
I’m very tired.
跟我来
Come with me.
走吧
Let's go.
请不要多想
Please don't think wrong about me.
我只想找个人说说话
I just need a company to talk.
如果有人这么跟我说话
If anyone talks to me like this,
我肯定会多想的
I will for sure thing wrongly.
到这来
Come here.
我又不会吃了你
I will not bite you.
她是我的妻子 罗西尼
She is my wife.Roshini
他是卡伦
and he is Karen.
我的儿子
My son.
你的妻子很漂亮
You wife is beautiful.
我和罗西尼过去一直很开心
I and Roshini use to be so happy.
然后发生了什么呢?
Then what happen?
卡伦
Karen.
能否有人无忧无虑呢?
Is everyone completely happy?
你快乐吗?
Are you happy?
偶尔吧
Had some moments.
你可以把过往种种视作云烟
You can leave all this now itself
然后开始新的生活
and start a new life.
没这么简单的 长官
It's not that easy, sir.
为什么?
Why?
跟你说了 你也不相信
If I tell you, you will not believe me.
说说看
Try to tell me.
下次吧
Some other time.
能帮我个忙吗 长官?
Can you do something for me, sir?
什么忙?
Do what?
你还记得马里卡吗?
Do you remember Malika?
沙希的女朋友
Shahsi's girlfriend.
她过得很不好
She is in a bad condition.
如果你能帮她一把就好了
If you can help her.
为什么? 她怎么了?
Why? What happen to her?
现在闭上眼睛
Now close you eyes.
喂 听着 把马里卡叫出来
Hey, listen, bring Malika.
遵命 长官
Ok, sir.
马里卡在哪里?
Where is Malika?
我就是这里唯一的马里卡
I'm the only Malika here.
你有何贵干?
Why you are here?
工作需要
It's a police matter.
把她叫出来
Call her.
她出去了
She has gone out.
你最好给她打电话 不然我就拿搜查令来
Better call her, if not I will bring warrent.
让你关门歇业
and close down you business.
是谁干的?
Who did this to you?
沙希之前把我赎了出来 长官
Shashi has bought me from them, sir.
这个女人现在却抵赖了 长官
Now this woman is denying, sir,
她强迫我干活
forceing me to work.
你自由了 到车里去吧
You are free, go and sit in the car.
这个人不会放我走的
This people will not let me go.
不用担心
Don't worry about that.
到车里去坐着就好
Just go and sit in the car.
快点!
Hurry!
你不用害怕
Don't have to be scared.
喂 你想去哪里
Hey,where are you going?
抓住她
Catch her.
听到没有 滚回屋里去
Do you hear me?go back to the house.
让我存一下档 好吗?
Let me keep this in the file, ok?
她是一个好人
She is a good woman.
她会帮助你的
She will help you.
长官
Sir.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不用谢我 谢谢洛奇吧
Don't thank me, thank Rozy.
是她告诉我你的情况
She infomed me about you.
洛奇?
Rozy?
谁是洛奇?
Who is Rozy?
洛奇在你的鸨母那里工作
Rozy's working with your madam.
我不知道你说的是谁
I don't know about whom are you talking.
干我们这行的
Its commen in our job
可能今天叫洛奇 明天就叫卡米莉
today Rozy and tomorrow Camelie.
这是常有的事情
This is what happens.
长官
Sir.
我向你撒谎了 长官
I lied to you, sir.
沙希跟阿尔曼·卡普尔早就认识
Shashi knew Armaan Kapoor.
事发当晚
On the night of his accident.
沙希见了他一面
Shashi met him.
你知道原因吗?
Do you know for what?
我从不过问他的工作
I have never interfer in his work,
你把塔姆尔抓起来
Do this, go and arrast Tamoor.
他肯定知情
I confirm he know.
沙希帮他做了很多事情
Shashi did so much for him.
鸨母的人把我抓走的时候 他却袖手旁观
He never helped me when madams people were taking me.
塔姆尔从来不这么做
Tamoor doesn't do this.
沙希跟你时常联系的 伙计
Shashi used to call you, brother.
他当时在偷沙希的东西
He was stealing Shashi's things.
是什么东西?
What things?
一个绿色的包 长官
It was a green bag, sir.
沙希那天晚上带回来的
Which Shashi brought that night.
明天早上十一点 独自到火车站来!
Tomorrow morning at 11 be at the rail station. Alone!
记得一个人过来 带上钱
Make sure you bring the cash along.
我会通知你见面地点
I will inform you where to meet.
给我记住了
Keep this in mind,
如果沙希的事情发生在我身上
if anything happen to me like Shahsi,
不管是否是故意为之 我都会把证据交给警察
with or without for fault, I will send the prove to police station.
明白
Ok.
我还要工作 你想要什么?
I have work to do. What do you want?
我需要你帮个忙
I need your help.
帮忙?
My help?
我不能相信别人
I can't trust anyone else.
听着 我不想趟这趟浑水
Look here, I don't want to get involved. Ok?
尼尔马拉
Nirmala.
如果计划成功
If what I'm planning works,
我们就能永远摆脱这种生活
we will be able to get out of this life.
像鸟一样自由
Free like birds.
想想吧
Think about it.
我不知道该相信谁 你还是我?
I do not know who can be trusted, you or me?
噢
Oh, you.
你好?
Hello?
给我听好
Listen carefully.
你的右手边有个公共厕所
On your right hand is a public toilet.
里面有个蓝色背包 把钱放在包里 明白吗?
There is a blue beg there keep the money there, get it?
明白了
I get it.
然后到四号站台
And then go to platform 4.
五分钟后 火车进站
And the after 5 minute the train will come,
然后你就上车
then claim that train,
赶紧去吧 最好别误了车
better be going before you miss the train.
# 不知道 #
# 你也如此 #
# 在哪个时刻 #
# 上帝会如何抉择 #
# 在这名为人生的赌局之中 #
# 我们会赢得什么 #
# 我们会失去什么 #
嗨 亲爱的
Hi darling.
把包给我吧
good give me the beg.
你为谁工作?
You are working for who?
告诉我
Tell me.
我会给你很多钱
I will give you lots of money.
我会给你比这里的都多
I will pay you more then this.
听着
Listen.
你这是在犯错
you are doing a mistake.
# 不知道 #
# 你也如此 #
# 在哪个时刻 #
# 上帝会如何抉择 #
# 在这名为人生的赌局之中 #
# 我们会赢得什么 #
# 我们会失去什么 #
# 幸福在哪里 #
# 幸福就在阴影之下 #
# 面带微笑之人 #
# 常常饱含泪水 #
# 无论你去哪里 #
# 脚下是熟悉的土地 #
# 头顶是熟悉的天空 #
# 不知道 #
# 你也如此 #
# 在哪个时刻 #
# 上帝会如何抉择 #
# 在这名为人生的赌局之中 #
# 我们会赢得什么 #
# 我们会失去什么 #
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
别人我不相信
I can't trust anyone else.
我不知道该相信谁 你还是我
I do not know who can be trusted you or me.
听着 你必须装作
Listen, you have to do acting
不认识我
as you do not know me.
别跟我说话
Do not talk to me.
是他
That's him.
抓住他!
Catch him!
钱在哪里?
Where is the money?
他一个人 先生
He is working alone, sir.
他告诉我们
He told us, sir.
他和沙希是同伙
He was working with shashi.
他是偶然看到了CD
He by chance saw the CD.
事实上 他根本不知道你的名字
In fact, he don't even know your name.
他从沙希的sim卡上得到你的号码
He got your number from shashi's sim.
杀了他!
Kill him!
完事之后 我会把钱给你们
I will pay your money after the job is done,
今天过后再也不要打这个号码
and after today never call me again.
你有没有想起过我?
Did you ever thought of me?
即使一次
Even once.
我什么都没有做
I did not do anything.
你以前说把我当朋友
You used to tell me that you are my friend.
我什么都没有做
I did not do anything.
在那里... 那里有人
Over there ... There is a man.
我会来的
I will come.
但是如果我没能赶到 请不要等我
But if I don't, please don't wait for me.
不论发生什么 一定要上车
Whatever happens, go into the train.
你一定不能误了火车
Make sure you don't miss the train.
西姆兰
Simran.
他提到了一个名字 叫西姆兰
He mentioned Simran's name.
西姆兰
Simran.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
他说了西姆兰 然后就死了
He mentioned Simran and then died.
长官 刚刚医院打来电话
sir, just got a call from the hospital.
坏蛋现在神智清醒了
The bad guy is conscious now.
我们现在可以审问了 我现在可以走了吗?
We can question him now, can I go now?
不 我去
No, I will go.
你带拉尼去见鸨母
You do this, take Ranni and meet Madam.
塔姆尔死前一直在说西姆兰
Tamoor before dying mentioned a name Simran.
去查查塔姆尔认识的人中谁叫西姆兰
Investigate who is Simran which Tamoor knew.
我肯定她是老鸨的女孩 带她过来
I'm sure she is madam's girl, bring her here.
你只有肯合作 才能获得自由
You will only be free if you coperate.
如果不合作 我们就把你关押起来
If you don't you will be behind bars.
你能听见长官跟你说话吗?
Can't you hear what sir is asking you?
长官 病人仍然很虚弱
Sir, patient is still critical.
你出去
You go out, please.
请让我工作
Let me do my work.
出去! 出去!
Get out! Out!
现在没人能救你了
No body can save you now.
如果你很幸运活下来了
If you are lucky and stay alive.
听好下面的事 首先我要关你进监狱
Listen what will happen. 1st I will prison you,
然后审问你
then I will question you.
从未有人对我撒过谎
I have never fail to get right answers,
我会准备一个案子起诉你
then I will prepare a case against you.
塔姆尔谋杀案件
Tamoor's murder case,
我会让你被判绞刑
and I will make sure you get hang sentence.
我保证你被判绞刑
I guaranty you get it.
他是警方的一个证人
He was a police witness.
你在犯罪现场被逮
Now you are caught red handed.
想想吧
Think about it.
如果你肯合作
If you corporate,
我可以让你免受死刑
I can save you from death sentance,
你最好告诉我谁指使你的
so better tell me who's dirt were you cleaning.
把他带出去 他不想死在这里
Take him out of here, he don't want to die here.
长官
Sir.
医生说他不能离开这里
Doctor said he can't be discarged.
告诉医生 他没有这回事
Tell the doctor he has mention no such thing.
我今天就要拘留这个人
I need this man in my custody by today.
把导管都拔掉
Remove everything all the paip and tiubs.
桑杰·基格里沃
Sanjay Gigriwal.
什么?
What?
桑杰·基格里沃
Sanjay Gigriwal.
长官 没有西姆兰这个人
Sir, there is no Simran here.
没有 长官
No, sir.
这里曾有过一个叫西姆兰的女孩
Ya, there was a girl named Simran
但是她几年前就离开了
but she ran away a few years back.
肯定有人知道她去哪里
Where did she go sure somebody knows.
或者她还在那里 有人想救她
or maybe she is still there and there are someone trying to save her.
叫拉尼在那里收集情报
Ask Ranni to be there and keep an eye.
是的 长官
Ok, sir.
你回警局
And you go back to the station,
带一支小队去桑杰的屋子 在那里见我
and get a team to Sanjay house and meet me there.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
警官先生
Inspector, sir.
你为什么来这里?
How come you are here?
基格里沃先生 逮捕令上有你的名字
Mr Gigriwal I have an arrest warrant on your name.
什么?
What?
什么罪名
What's the charge?
谋杀塔姆尔和沙希
For Tamoor and Shashi's murder.
你认识巴布·迪普奈吗?
Do you know Babbu Dipnes?
他作证受你指使
He testified against you.
你得跟我走一趟
You have to follow me.
把你的手机给我
Please pass me your mobile phone.
我们走
Let's go.
站起来
Stand up.
拜托了
Please.
给我一分钟
One minute.
我们能谈谈吗?
Can we talk?
说吧
Talk.
单独谈
Alone.
就在这里说
Talk in front of everyone.
他敲诈我们
He was blackmailing us.
这件事情起于三年之前
All this started 3 years back.
西姆兰 我 还有我们的好友尼卡尔
Armaan, me and our friend Nikhal
去参加一个聚会
was going to a party.
单身汉聚会 我该带谁啊?
What should me take along on a bacelour party?
尼卡尔认识沙希
Nikhal knew Shashi.
我们去里多饭店
Let's go Hotel Lido.
你好 沙希
Hello Shashi.
我们跟他去了里多饭店
We went Hotel Lido with him
从那里带走了一个女孩
and from there we picked up a girl.
我并不想这么做
I was not happy with this.
那个女孩叫什么?
What was the girls name?
西姆兰
Simran.
尼卡尔开始在车里调戏那个女孩
Nikhal started flirting in the car.
我能试试吗?
Can I try?
接下来怎么样了?
What happen next?
不知道
Don't know.
我不知道是车门没关好还是...
I'm not sure the cars door was not close properly or...
事故就这样发生了
It was an accident.
尼卡尔
Nikhal.
一切都会没事的
Nothing will happen to you.
阿尔曼上车
Armaan get into the car now.
桑杰 这种情况下我们不能丢下她不管
Sanjay, we can't leave her in this condition.
如果再等 我们会因这个婊子惹麻烦的
Will be in trouble becouse of this prostitude if we wait.
到车里坐下 拜托
Sit in the car, please.
我们不能丢下她 她会死的
We can’t leave her she will die.
给沙希打电话 他会照顾好她的
Call Shashi and he will take care of her.
一周之后 沙希打电话给阿尔曼
After a week, Shashi called Armaan.
第二天他寄了一张DVD来
Then the next day he send a DVD.
那是饭店闭路电视的录像
It was a recording of the Hotel CCTV,
录像里面我们三人带着那个女孩穿过大厅
in that recording we 3 were seen with the girl at the lobby.
他告诉我们那个女孩死了
He told us the girl died
他把她埋在了某个地方
and he has buried her body some way.
DVD在哪里?
Where is the DVD?
我认识这个女孩
I know this girl.
她告诉我们所有的信息
She is the one who gave me all the information.
她还活着?
Is she still alive?
是的
Yes, she is.
我和她见过好多次
I have met her many times.
我肯定沙希和那女孩帮你处理了
I'm sure that Shashi and the girl have fix you up.
但是如果她也受到牵连 为什么她要帮你?
But why will she help you if she is involved?
只有她能回答我
Only she can answer me.
达夫拉 现在去里多饭店
Devraj, go to Hotel Lido now.
你在那里会见到她 她现在叫洛奇不叫西姆兰
You will meet her there and she is Rozy nowadays not Simran
通知拉尼
and do inform Ranni too.
带她到你见到她的警察局
Bring her to station once you see her.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
我们走
Let’s go.
一开始你接到电话的时候就该报警
Should have informed the police when 1st you received the call.
很多人都能得救
A lot of lives would have been saved.
也许阿尔曼的生命也能
Maybe even Armaan's life too.
做了这么多事 你得到了什么?
What did you gain doing all this?
是的 先生 我们把西卡瓦特先生带到了警署
Yes, sir. We will bring Mr Shekawat to the police station.
长官 我感觉我看见她了
Sir, I feel like I can only see her.
你疯了吗?
Are you in your senses?
那你现在告诉我 她是个幽灵
Now you will tell me that she is a ghost.
听着 别以为我错了
Look, don't think me wrong.
我们整个警察局都很尊重你
We all police department respects you a lot.
但是现在人们都在议论你 这对你的事业不利
But now people are talking about you which is bad for you career.
你的下属说你不睡觉
Your own staff is talking that you don't sleep.
每天晚上都梦游
Every night you are going around.
自言自语
And you been talking alone.
猜别人怎么看
See how everyone is looking,
他们一定认为今天我带你出去乐了
They must be thinking that today I'm going for fun with you.
我为什么要说谎?
Why will I lie?
这里的人不会帮警察
People here don't help police.
想想你的未来 西卡瓦特
Think about your furtue, Shekawat.
不管你怎么说
What ever you are saying
如果你写了份报告 会怎么样?
If you file a report, what's going to happen?
整个部门都会笑话你
The whole department will make fun of you.
你休两个月假
You take 2 months break.
你需要放假
You really need it.
那真相呢?
How about the truth?
真相就是...
The truth is...
基格里沃不想进监狱 所以他自杀了
That Gigriwal did not want to go to prison and he suicide.
阿尔曼·卡普尔的事故是一个解不开的迷
Armaan Kapoor's accident is a unsolved case.
敲诈者也死了
And the blackmailers are also death.
案子结了
Case's closed.
这就是真相
This is the truth.
这就是你的陈词
And this will be your statement.
明白吗?
Am I clear?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
很好
Good.
你为什么还在这里 洛奇?
Why are you still here, Rozy?
这个地方不适合你
This place does not suit you.
我在等你
I was waiting for you.
来带我离开这里
That when you will come and take me away from here.
苏尔扬 听着 你要听你自己的
Surjan, listen you need to curve yourself.
如果不这样 你会更痛苦
If not you will suffer more,
他们被我们这样的人吸引
They get attracted with people like us,
他们觉得我们也像他们一样
They feel we are also like them.
我能带走你的所有烦恼
I can take away all your worries,
有些人可以和灵魂说话
But some people can talk to souls.
我在书中读到过
I have read in books.
试着用你的脑子想想 罗西尼
Try to think Roshini, use you brain.
你怎么能相信这样的鬼话?
How could you believe in such non sense?
这个世界上有许多东西无法解释
There are a lots of things in this world which can't be explained
你可以把这些都丢下
You can leave all this
开始新的生活
and start a new life.
这不那么容易 先生
It's not that easy, sir.
为什么?
Why?
如果我告诉你 你就不会相信我了
If I tell you, you will not believe me.
我们走
Let's go.
我会带你到一个任何人都见不到我们的地方
I will take you to a place where nobody will be able to see us.
如果你想要 我就能帮你
If you want, I can help you.
真的?
Really?
你能为我做什么?
What can you do for me?
我知道你会回来
I knew it you will come back.
人死后 灵魂仍会在周围
After dying the souls are still around.
只有它们能变成人形
Only they can transform to human form.
对那些不存在的人呢?
How about for those who don't exist?
它们怎么能消失呢?
How can they diserpear?
三年前我的朋友和几个男人出去
3 years back my friend when out with some guys,
她没有回来
and she did not return.
想想吧 先生
Something to think about right, sir.
一个女孩消失了 没人关心她的死活
A girl diserpears and nobody cares.
这是个什么地方?
What place is this?
这是我的地方
This is my place.
没人来过
Nobody comes here.
如果你找不到我
If you can't find me,
在这里就能找到了
you will find me here.
你为什么不明白 苏里?
Why you don't uderstand, Suri?
卡伦想跟你说说话
Karen wants to talk to you.
我怎么知道
How I know, sir
也许有一天我能帮到你?
maybe one day I can help you?
你好 爸爸
Hello, Dada.
我想你
I miss you.
我知道你也想我
I know you miss me too.
不管那天发生了什么
Whatever happened that day.
那不是你的错
It was not your mistake.
是我的错 爸爸
It was my mistake, Dada.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你改变不了任何事情
There was nothing you could do to change anything.
我只想告诉你这些
I just wanted to tell you this.
请不要自责
Please do not blame yourself.
我感到很受伤
I feel hurt.
不要因为我 跟妈妈打架
Don't fight with mama, becouse of me.
如果你和妈妈一直高兴
If you and mama stay happy,
我也会很高兴
I will be also happy then.
爸爸 记得你曾经告诉我
Dada, do you remember you use to tell me
你想一直看见我高兴吗?
that you want to see me happy always?
我知道 你会把所有事都办好的
I know, that you will make everything allright.
你是这个世界上最好的爸爸
You are the best Dada in this world.
深影字幕组欢迎您 深影论坛 shinybbs.com
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
翻译：  Echo 莫若謙 好战青蛙 五枚の夜堇 将错就错
校对：  爽爷     后期： 小滔
# 就算全世界告诉我 #
# 你已离去#
# 但是你在这里 #
# 此时此刻 你在这里 #
# 就算全世界告诉我 #
# 你已离去#
# 但是你在这里 #
# 此时此刻 你在这里 #
# 在我所有的思绪之中 #
# 每一句说出的话语 #
# 在我所有的感情之中 #
# 每一个表现的表情 #
# 你是唯一 #
# 你是一切 #
# 就算全世界告诉我 #
# 你已离去#
# 但是你在这里 #
# 此时此刻 你在这里 #
# 就算全世界告诉我 #
# 你已离去#
# 但是你在这里 #
# 此时此刻 你在这里 #
# 你不曾真正离我而去 #
# 即便今日 你也握着我的双手 #
# 无论目的何方 #
# 你是我的伴侣 #
# 一路到底 #
# 就算全世界告诉我 你已离去#
# 但是你在这里 #
# 此时此刻 你在这里 #
# 就算全世界告诉我 你已离去#
# 但是你在这里 #
# 此时此刻 你在这里 #